

amy.hanv@gmail.com +1 (604) 902 6111 github.com/amyhanv 1102-728 Yates St, Victoria BC, V8W0C8

A software developer with strong communication and organizational skills and B.Sc. in Computer Science with a focus in front-end development and eye for design. Experienced in developing full-stack web applications and front-end React components and web pages to match design mock-ups. Comfortable with Agile methodologies and remote work.

Work Experience

Junior Software Developer

Dyspatch

Feb 2020 - Present Victoria, BC

- Develop new features on Dyspatch in a full-stack manner, adding new components and UI updates (React, Typescript) to adding back-end endpoints (Golang) and database migrations (SQL).
 - Integrate Stripe to support purchasing a subscription within Dyspatch.
- Implement front-end and back-end unit (Jest and Golang), integration, and E2E tests (Cypress) when working on a new feature or fixing a bug, prioritize test coverage to catch any future regressions.
- Collaborate closely with the design team to develop smooth and beautiful UI, vigilant for improvements in userexperience, and implementing components to match design mockups.
- Participate in cross-team meetings in feature scoping for upcoming tasks and Epics with technical owners to plan and prioritize the Agile technical roadmap.
- Lead team meetings over Zoom and take the initiative to coordinate any meetings with team members and designers to discuss technical implementaions and UI.

DeveloperCo-op | May 2019 - Aug 2019
Momentum
Victoria, BC

- Developed the Momentum "New Tab" Chrome extension with over 3 million downloads and user-facing
 Momentum Team, using Vue and BackboneJS.
- Built modular, reusable Vue and Backbone components with industry best practices for scalability and maintainability
- Implemented automated testing for application functionality, design, and behaviour with Cypress Created API endpoints and DB model (SQL) to save user feedback submissions Collaborated in an Agile team environment with daily Scrum meetings

Involvements

President

Sept 2017 - Jan 2020

UVic WebDev Club

- Organized clubs meetings and workshops
- Mentored club members with their projects, questions, or concerns
- Arranged hackathons and club events (e.g. HackUVic, HackathingUVic, UVic Spookathon,
- __ FiresideChat, etc.)
- Managed club group, website, social medias, and communications

Education

BSc Computer Science

Sept 2014 - Jan 2020

University of Victoria

- Software Engineering Option
- Co-ops
- Relevant coursework:
 - Data Visualization, Databases, Computer
 Communications & Networks, Human-Computer
 Interaction, Documentation